Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers, 1963 - 2016 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
Nick Zedd Papers
1937-2016
1979-2008
Fales Library and Special Collections
Zedd, Nick
MSS.311
28.35 Linear Feet
Nick Zedd is a filmmaker, writer, actor, and artist who became the leading figure of the Cinema of Transgression Movement (1984 - 1990). The Nick Zedd Papers preserve Zedd's films and writing, which include scripts, notebooks, sketchbooks, photographs, and audio and moving image elements.
Biographical Note
Nick Zedd (James Harding) was born in Takoma Park, Maryland in 1956. He attended The Philadelphia College of Art for illustration and printmaking, studied animation at The School of Visual Arts, and earned a BFA in film at The Pratt Art Institute. Zedd used the phrase "The Cinema of Transgression" (1984 - 1990) to describe an underground network of New York City filmmakers and performance artists known for low-budget productions exploring themes of erotica, violence, and humor. This community included Zedd, Tessa Hughes-Freeland, Richard Kern, Lung Leg, Lydia Lunch, Kembra Pfahler, Casandra Stark, and Tommy Turner. Zedd wrote, illustrated, designed, and published The Underground Film Bulletin (1984 - 1990) pseudonymously to document his work and the work of this community. Zedd also used this forum to develop ideas that would become "The Cinema of Transgression Manifesto," and later, "The Theory of Xenomorphosis." Zedd published autobiographical works Bleed (1992) and Totem of the Depraved (1996) as well as contributed to periodicals including Film Threat, The East Village Eye, CUZ, and Penthouse Magazine. Zedd has been a visiting lecturer at various film, art, and poetry festivals in the United States, as well as in Sweden and Germany.
Zedd acted in various films, including Richard Kern's "The Manhattan Love Suicides" (1985), Alyce Wittenstein's "No Such Thing as Gravity" (1989), Ari Roussimoff's "Shadows in the City" (1990), Rachel Amodeo's "What About Me" (1993), Peter Sempel's "Jonas in the Desert" (1994), and Peter Strickland's "Bubblegum" (1995). As a filmmaker, Zedd cites the work of Ed Wood Jr., Jack Smith, and John Waters as primary influences. Zedd's films have been featured in exhibitions and festivals at The Anthology Film Archives, The Whitney Museum of American Art, The Museum of Modern Art, and in theatres and universities in Australia, Canada, England, Germany, Italy, Norway, and Sweden. With performance artist Saint Reverend Jen, Zedd created the satirical sci-fi public access television series "The Adventures of Electra Elf" (2002 - 2008). His work is also featured in the documentaries "Llik Your Idols" (2007) and "Blank City" (2010).
Filmography
"They Eat Scum" (1979)
"The Bogus Man" (1980)
"Geek Maggot Bingo" (1983)
"The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" (1983)
"School of Shame" (1984)
"Thrust in Me" (1984)
"Kiss Me Goodbye" (1985)
"Go to Hell" (1985)
"Police State" (1987)
"I Shit on God" (1988)
"Whoregasm" (1988)
"War is Menstrual Envy" (1992)
"Smiling Faces Tell Lies" (1995)
"Screen Tests/Why Do You Exist" (1998)
"Tom Thumb in the Land of the Giants" (1999)
"Ecstasy in Entropy" (1999)
"I of K9" (2001)
"Elf Panties: The Movie" (2001)
"Lord of the Cockrings" (2001)
"Thus Spake Zarathustra" (2001)
"I Was a Quality of Life Violation" (2002)
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
The donor has mandated that self-shot photography by researchers is not permitted for this collection. If a researcher needs a reference image for the purpose of requesting permission to reproduce from Nick Zedd, a Fales staff member will photograph the requested items and send the reference images to Zedd on the researcher's behalf.
Arrangement
Within each series, materials are either arranged alphabetically by project title or chronologically if dated.
Series I: Writing includes the work of Nick Zedd and others, and is organized alphabetically by project title.
Subseries A: Zedd A - Z includes original journals, manuscripts, poetry, and scripts, including unrealized productions "The Deprogramming" (1981) and "Thimble of Oblivion" (1983) intended to star Richard Hell, Jack Smith, and Zedd.
Subseries B: Juvenelia includes artistic compositions completed during Zedd's youth and an assortment of student materials. Secret Agent Freddy is an illustrated comic strip for a character based on James Bond and Man from "U.N.C.L.E," while 25th Century Magazine was based on Famous Monsters Magazine. Venusian Press is a collaboration between Zedd and his brother John Harding while the Harding Film Production Catalogs were inspired by Castle Films and intended to promote Zedd's childhood films "Attack of the Giant Fly" (1968), "The Return of the Giant Fly" (1970), "The Giant Fly Invincible" (1971), and "Psy-Color" (1970).
Subseries C: Source and Subject Files include documentation directly related to the previous subseries, in addition to development files dedicated to subjects or individuals of interest, as either source material or collaborative parties.
Subseries D: Other Authors includes essays, poetry, scripts, and screenplays not written by Zedd.
Series II: Projects documents the production development of films involving Zedd and the publishing process of his written works. Elements are organized by document type and alphabetically by project title or subject, then chronologically.
Subseries A: Development includes administrative and pre-production documents.
Subseries B: Distribution contains post-production and distribution materials, including ephemera, flyers, posters and festival programs.
Subseries C: Interviews preserves restrospective press about Zedd.
Subseries D: Ads, Reviews and Literature includes ad spots, project press, and literature that includes discussion of Zedd's work and The Cinema of Transgression Movement.
Subseries E: Other Artists and Events contains promotional material of events not featuring Zedd's work.
Series III: Correspondence preserves communication not directly related to any single production, and is organized alphabetically by individual or company in contact, then chronologically.
Subseries A: Professional
Subseries B: Personal
Series IV: Dad's Pornography Collection preserves Zedd's father's work as a United States Postal Service censorship researcher. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject and document type.
Series V: Photography contains photographs, contact sheets, negatives, and slides pertaining to Zedd's productions and personal collection.
Subseries A: Professional
Subseries B: Personal
Series VI: Illustrations and Artwork includes Zedd's original comic illustrations, collages, and paintings.
Series VII: Objects contains an assortment of props and production materials, Zedd-Casanova Clothing, and "The Mexican Kit."
Subseries A: Props
Subseries B: Zedd - Casanova Clothing includes a variety of tops and pleated skirts featuring prints from Zedd's filmography, and the original screenprint stencils. Designed by Nick Zedd and his wife Monica Casanova.
Subseries C: The Mexican Kit is an assortment of personal items Zedd collectively titled "The Mexican Kit." This assemblage includes a miniature piñata, ornaments, household adornments, sugar skulls, and figurines.
Series VIII: Film includes original filmic elements by Zedd and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically. Access copies appropriate for consultation are not currently available.
Subseries A: By Nick Zedd
Subseries B: Original Containers
Subseries C: Juvenelia and Family Films include films Zedd completed as a youth, in addition to a collection of Harding Family movies.
Subseries D: Miscellaneous Film includes Lung Leg's "Worm Movie" and a collection of commercial films from Zedd's personal collection.
Series IX: Video includes original moving image elements by Zedd and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically. Access copies appropriate for consultation may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: By Nick Zedd
Subseries B: Acting and Press preserves Zedd's acting work, in addition to interviews and documentaries about the Cinema of Transgression by other filmmakers.
Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes assorted footage from Zedd's personal video library, rare work by his contemporaries and collaborators, as well as commercial works that Zedd collected.
Series X: Audio includes original audio elements by and or about Nick Zedd, and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically. Access copies appropriate for consultation may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Film Soundtracks include Zedd production sound effects reels.
Subseries B: Cassettes preserve Zedd's sound work and interview recordings.
Subseries C: Miscellaneous includes recordings from Zedd's personal collection.
Subseries D: Vinyl includes Zedd's work with the Zyklon Beatles and other commercial recordings from his personal collection.
Series XI: Data Storage includes Zedd's magnetic and optical computer data storage elements organized chronologically, then alphabetically.
Series XII: Accretions consists of materials added to the collection following initial arrangement and description.
Scope and Contents
The Nick Zedd Papers contain materials that document Zedd's film career, ranging from the late 1970s through 2008. This collection also preserves Zedd's writing, which includes scripts, notebooks, articles, essays, comics, poetry, and zine manuscripts that date back to Zedd's elementary education in the 1960s. Elements include source material for his writing career as well as distribution documents promoting both his filmic and writing works in the form of ephemera, flyers, festival programs, and posters. This body of components also includes the work and promotional documents of other artists, and the censorship and community standards research compiled by his father. In addition, this collection includes professional and personal correspondence, production and personal photography, original illustrations, sketchbooks, and original film, video, and audio recordings.
Separated Materials
The following biblography lists materials that have been separated and moved to the Fales Downtown Collection and to the Bobst general stacks. This list is organized by item type, then alphabetically. Records for these items can also be retrieved through a "related name" search in, NYU's online catalog.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Nick Zedd in 2011, with multiple accretions given in 2013 and 2016. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are: 2011.311, 2013.311.001, 2013.311.002, and 2016.013.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Cinema of Transgression.; No wave (cinema); Punk culture -- New York (State) -- New York; Independent filmmakers -- United States.; Pornography -- Social aspects.; Anthology Film Archives.; Downtown Collection.; Downtown writers.; Sprinkle, Annie, 1954-; Lunch, Lydia; Wojnarowicz, David; Waters, John, 1946-; Hell, Richard; Kern, Richard, 1954-; Zedd, Nick
- Series I: Writing
  Scope and Content
  Series I: Writing includes the work of Nick Zedd and others, and is organized alphabetically by project title.
  Subseries A: Zedd A - Z includes original journals, manuscripts, poetry, and scripts, including unrealized productions "The Deprogramming" (1981) and "Thimble of Oblivion" (1983) intended to star Richard Hell, Jack Smith, and Zedd.
  Subseries B: Juvenelia includes artistic compositions completed during Zedd's youth and an assortment of student materials. Secret Agent Freddy is an illustrated comic strip for a character based on James Bond and Man from "U.N.C.L.E," while 25th Century Magazine was based on Famous Monsters Magazine. Venusian Press is a collaboration between Zedd and his brother John Harding while the Harding Film Production Catalogs were inspired by Castle Films and intended to promote Zedd's childhood films "Attack of the Giant Fly" (1968), "The Return of the Giant Fly" (1970), "The Giant Fly Invincible" (1971), and "Psy-Color" (1970).
  Subseries C: Source and Subject Files include documentation directly related to the previous subseries, in addition to development files dedicated to subjects or individuals of interest, as either source material or collaborative parties.
  Subseries D: Other Authors includes essays, poetry, scripts, and screenplays not written by Zedd.
  - Subseries A: Zedd A - Z
    - "1995, Chapter 1" (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Battle of the Bands" [Script], 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Becchky's Open Mouth Nite" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Deadly Little Trees" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Don't Worry Bee Happy" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Electra Elf, The Beginning" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Elf Flakes Commercial" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Gone With the Mind" [Script, copy 1], 2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Gone With the Mind" [Script, copy 2], 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Great Shrunken Expectations" [Script], 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Hell Bound Heiresses" [Script], 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Hollow Be Thy Name" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf and Fluffer, Episode 3: I, Nauseous" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: King Neptune/Old Man and the Sea Monkey, Of Lice and Men" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf, Episode 4: Maggot on a Hot Tin Roof" [Script], 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Of Lice and Men" [Script], 2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: The Price is Wrong" [Script], 2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Roof Party" [Script], undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Vile Buddies" [Script], 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: [untitled script fragments], undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: We All Scream for Ice Cream" [Script], 2007 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: We All Scream for Ice Cream" [Revised Script], 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "A Liar is the Lowest Form of Human Life" for Film Threat #11, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - "Amato Opera" and "Mars Bar" for 10003 [Manuscript with Magazine], June 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - "Anarchaos" for Mohawk Beaver #8 [Zine], 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - "An Exercise in Futility," "Bleed," "Empire of Oblivion," "No More," "Totem of the Depraved," "War of Menstrual Envy" [Blue Notebook], undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - "Another Weekend in Hell: New York is a Hideous Place to be in the Summer", July 2, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - "Artists and Fleas" for 11211 [Manuscript with Magazine], May 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - "Bleed" [Manuscript with Biography], 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - "Bleed" [Green Notebook with Loose Notes], c1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - "Bleed" [Blue Notebook], undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - "Bleed" [Manuscript Fragments], c1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - "Bleed, Part 1" [Hanuman Books Edition], 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - "Bleed" for Crawl or Die! #13 [Magazine], undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - "The Bogus Man: Scene 1" [Manuscipt], undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - "Book by Zedd," "No Guilt," "From Entropy to Ecstasy" [Red Notebook], undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - "Born to Die: Conformity is Not Transgressive," Sacred Monster: The Elf Diaries" [Coverless Notebook], undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - "The Boy Who Cried Wolf: GG Allin" for Sampling the City: The Portable Lower East Side Volume 11, Number 1, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - "The Carnal Carnivore," for Penthouse Magazine [Manuscript], 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - "Cinema of Transgression Manifesto" for Crimson Celluloid #5 [Manuscript with Zine], undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - "Clonespiracy" [Notes Removed from Johnny Satan Sketchbook], undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - "Conspire," "Who Would Jesus Bomb?" "You're Already Dead" for 11211 [Manuscript with Magazine], March 2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - "Curse of the Crypt Scrypt" by Jim Harding and Dave Corridon [Manuscript], undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - "A Cursed Night in Nuremberg" for Riot Cinema, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - "Dear Feminists, Re: Thrust in Me", undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - "The Deprogramming" [Manuscript], 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - "Direct Democracy is Protest", November 2000 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - "Divide and Conquer," "What Would You Do if You Could Play God for One Day?" [With Notes], undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - "Donna Death 1979" (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - "Dream", undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - "Ed Wood: An Appreciation", undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - "Eulogy" for Master Bator, Naked Reality Meltdown Issue 3 [Manuscript with Magazine], October 1991 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - "Experimental Movies Today," "The Cinema of Transgression Manifesto", undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - "Film [Doire]", 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - "The Freak From Suckweasel Mountain/Geek Maggot Bingo (Monster Movie)" [Manuscript], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - "The Freak From Suckweasel Mountain" [Synopsis with Notes], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - "Freedom of Expression National Monument" [with Research Elements], c2004 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - "Freedumb/What is a Pre-Emptive Strike?" for Alternative Screen #2 [Magazine], April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - "From Entropy to Ecstasy" [Uncorrected Manuscript], May 20, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "From Entropy to Ecstasy, Chapter 7" for Bil Bok [Magazine], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Fuck You", undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Generation Tech," "No Guilt" [Blue Notebook], 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "Germany: The Girl in the Tight, Wet Dress" for Penthouse Letters [Magazine], May 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "GG Allin R.I.P." for Play God New Orleans [Manuscript with Zine], 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "God Hates NYC Fags", undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "A Guide to NY Filmmakers", undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "HAL Festival" for 10003 [Magazine], August 2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - "Hallucinations of a Homeless Filmmaker", undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Hatred of Capitalism, #1, April 2013 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - "I Assert a New Language" [Annotated Bangladeshi Prayer Book], undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - "In Blood and Darkness", undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - "It's Only a Movie: Cecil B. Demented", c2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - "Johnny Satan" [Black Sketchbook], c1976 (Box 13, Item 1)
    - "Keep the East Village Beautiful Campaign" [Commercial Script], undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - "A Letter From a New York Jail" for Mohawk Beaver #7 [Manuscript with Zine], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - "Listen Asshole, You're Dead Wrong About Rap" for Conflict 49 [Zine], Winter 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - "The Legend of Johnny Satan" [Synopsis Removed from Oversized Sketchbook], undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - "Letter to the President to Stop the Cycle of Violence", 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - "Life: The Great Indulgence, Death: The Great Abstinence" [Notes with Research], c2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - "The Little Bitch" By Nick Zedd and Audrey Rose for Jicket Teen Murder Magazine [Manuscript with Magazine], c1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - "Lydia's Touch (Conclusion)" [With Notes and Related Works], c1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - "Lydia's Touch" by Nick Zedd with "Vampire's Kiss" by Lydia Lunch for Penthouse Hot Talk [Magazine], September - October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - "Mace. How Low Can You Go?" [Manuscript With Notes], undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - "Making a Mountain Out of a Mole Hill" for 11211 [Manuscript with Magazine], 2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - "Man Eaters: Volume 101 - 102" Reviews [Manuscript], undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - "Mars Bar", c2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - "Me Minus You" By Nick Zedd, Phoebe LeGere, and Jessica Jason [Script], 1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - "My Bar Hop From Hell" for 11211 [Manuscript with Magazine], May 2005 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - "My Month in Kim's Gulag", undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - "New York 1997" for Bilk Bok [Manuscript with Magazine] (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - "Nick Zedd" for Progress Report [Zine], Ocotber 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - [Nick Zedd on Jack Smith, Assorted Works], April - May 1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - "Night of the Lady Wrestlers", undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - "Nightmare in Goteborg," "Part II: The Chilling Effect", undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - "No Guilt" [Composition Notebook], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - "No Guilt" [Blue Notebook], c1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - "No Guilt" [Red Notebook], c1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - "No Guilt, Chapter 1", 2000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - "No Guilt, Chapter Nine" for Bil Bok #7 [Magazine], 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - "No More, Chapter One" [Manuscript], undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - "No More" for Culture Post Mortem [Zine], undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - "Notes From an Infidel" [Notes with Research], c2004 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - "Our Sorry State of the Union" for 11211 [Magazine], March 2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - "Pandora's Box" for Penthouse Forum [Magazine], October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - "Part II: The Puke of Oslo", undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - "The Perfect Woman" by Nick Zedd and Lydia Lunch, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - "Plane Flight" [Script], undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - [Poetry], undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - "Police State" [Script Fragments with Source Material], undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - "Public Access TV is Under Attack", undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - "Query: Roman Porno From Japan", undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - "The Read Cafe" for 11211 [Manuscript and Magazine], July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - "Rick Strange, Ugly", undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - "Ritual of Entropy: The Pagan Ash Notwithstanding", undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - "Scarred" by Nick Zedd and Gia Genocide, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - "Scenes for Video (Not in Sequence)", undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - "Script Writing Directors Workshop Class Notes", undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - "Shaolin Comix" [Manuscript], 1999 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - "Shaolin Comix" for The Mower [Journal with Comic Book Supplement], 1993 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - "Shaolin in Doodyville" for East Village Sampler [Zine], 2006 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - "Sinbad Glick in New Atlantis (With Apologies to Jack Smith, R.I.P.)" for 11211 [Script with Magazine], May 2003 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - "St. Marks Bars" for 10003 [Magazine], December 2004 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - "Still Banned In Canada" [Manuscript], undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - "Tempest" [Script Fragments with Notes, Cat Folder], c2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Theory of Xenomorphosis" [Manuscript on Penetration Films Letterhead], undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Theory of Xenomorphosis" for Bil Bok #10 [Magazine], 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "Theory of Xenomorphosis" for Night #42 [Magazine], 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "There Goes Your Neighborhood", May 13, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)